A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Accessions 1997-2008, Record Group 4 FA785
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant and Grantee Files, 1971-1999; 2; 52.48 Cubic Feet
  - Deer Creek Foundation, 1991-1994 (Box 135, Folder 25)
  - Defense Budget Project, 1992-1994 (Box 135, Folder 26)
  - Defense, Secretary of (United States Government), 1970 (Box 135, Folder 27)
  - University of Denver, 1977; 1981 (Box 135, Folder 28-29)
  - Detroit CATV, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 30)
  - Development Officers, 1977 (Box 135, Folder 31)
  - Development Studies Center, 1989-1995 (Box 135, Folder 32)
  - Diebold, Inc., 1975-1984 (Box 135, Folder 33)
  - The Discovery Channel, 1992-1993 (Box 135, Folder 34)
  - Drexel University, 1978-1994 (Box 136, Folder 1-3)
  - Duke University, 1992-1996 (Box 136, Folder 4-8)
  - Duke University - Joel Smith (92-134), 1992 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Duke University - Barber - Conduct of Modern Presidency and Meeting in New York at Plaza, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Duke University Medical Center - Grants through 1975, 1945-1975 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Duke University - July 1994 Meetings, North Carolina, 1994 June-July (Box 136, Folder 12-13)
  - E. Alden Dunham, 1991-1992 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Dun and Bradstreet, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - DVQ Association - Bower (D92218), 1992 (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - The Daniel Yankelovich Group (DYG, Inc.), 1986-1997 (Box 136, Folder 17-22)
  - The Daniel Yankelovich Group (DYG, Inc.) - Studies, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 23-24)
  - E - General, 1989-1995 (Box 136, Folder 25-27)
  - Ecoanalysis, Inc., 1992 (Box 136, Folder 28)
  - Educational Television - Newsletter, 1970 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1992-1997 (Box 137, Folder 2-3)
  - Educational Testing Service - William Turnbull, President, 1971-1983 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - EDUCOM, 1971-1990 (Box 137, Folder 5-10)
  - Elderworks, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Johanna Ehrich, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Elderly and Media, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Electronic Arts, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Electronic Town Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 137, Folder 14A-17)
  - Electronic Publishing - Dave Miller, 1988-1989 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - Emory University, 1990-1995 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Emory University - International Media and Communications Program, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - Entertainment Industries Council, Inc., 1993 (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - Etherage, Lloyd - General, 1997 (Box 137, Folder 22)
  - F - General, 1989-1996 (Box 137, Folder 23-29)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1989-1997 (Box 137, Folder 30-31)
  - Francis Dummer Fisher, 1988-1992 (Box 137, Folder 32)
  - Ford Foundation, 1982-1996 (Box 137, Folder 33-35)
  - Foundation for Advancement in Science and Education (FASE), 1993 (Box 137, Folder 36)
  - The Foundation Center, 1975-1993 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - The Foundation Center - Buckman (D90317), 1990 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - The Foundation Center - Buckman (D90317), 1990 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - The Foundation Center - Englehardt (D92214), 1991-1992 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - The Foundation Center - Buckman (D91320), 1991-1992 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - The Foundation Center - Buckman (D91108), 1990-1991 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - The Foundation Center - Englehardt (D93104), 1992-1993 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - The Foundation Center - Englehardt (D95107), 1994-1995 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - The Foundation Center - Englehardt (D95324), 1995-1996 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - The Foundation Center - Englehardt (D96320), 1996-1997 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - The Foundation Center - Englehardt (D97214), 1996-1998 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - The Foundation Center - Englehardt (D98103), 1997-1998 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Freedom Forum, 1991-1996 (Box 138, Folder 13-14)
  - Freewares and Sharewares, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Fox News Service, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Fund for the City of New York, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - G - General, 1987-1997 (Box 138, Folder 18-23)
  - Gannett Foundation Freedom Center, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 24)
  - Gannett Foundation Media Center, 1989-1993 (Box 138, Folder 25)
  - John Gardner, 1990-1994 (Box 138, Folder 26)
  - Geller, Henry (Box 138, Folder 27)
  - General Atlantic Partners, 1993-1994 (Box 138, Folder 28)
  - George Washington University, 1971-1993 (Box 139, Folder 1-6)
  - George Washington University - Brock (G91327), 1991-1994 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Gillette Global Communications, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - William T. Golden - Correspondence, 1981-1994 (Box 139, Folder 9-10)
  - Connie Goldman Productions, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Goldman Sachs, 1986-1992 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - William T. Grant Foundation, 1990-1992 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Grantmakers for Children and Youth, 1989-1990 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Lawrence Grossman, 1979; 1990-1992 (Box 139, Folder 15-16)
  - H - General, 1989-1997 (Box 139, Folder 17-23)
  - Hamilton, Rabinovitz and Alschuler, Inc., 1989-1996 (Box 139, Folder 24-25)
  - Hammett, William, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 26)
  - Harcourt Brace, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 27-28)
  - Harper Collins Publishers, 1994-1995 (Box 139, Folder 29-30)
  - Louis Harris Associates, 1991-1996 (Box 139, Folder 31-32)
  - Hartford Gunn Institute, 1976-1995 (Box 139, Folder 33-36)
  - Harvard University - General, 1972-1996 (Box 140, Folder 1-18)
  - Harvard University - Dubois Institute, Skip Gates, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - Harvard University - Center for Information Policy Resources, 1976-1994 (Box 140, Folder 20-34)
  - Ann Branscomb (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Harvard University - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1990-1995 (Box 141, Folder 2-3)
  - Harvard University - Graduate School of Education, 1979-1995 (Box 141, Folder 4-8)
  - Harvard University - JFK School of Government, 1990-1995 (Box 141, Folder 9-11)
  - Harvard University - Shorenstein Barone Center, 1987-1993 (Box 141, Folder 12-15)
  - Harvard University - JFK School of Government, 1988 (Box 141, Folder 16)
  - Harvard Law School, 1990-1995 (Box 141, Folder 17-18)
  - Harvard University - School of Public Health, 1970-1995 (Box 141, Folder 19-24)
  - Harvard University - Adatto (D92328) (Box 141, Folder 25)
  - Harvard University - Riesman-McLaughlin (G91328), 1992-1994 (Box 141, Folder 26)
  - Harvard University - Kalb-Adatto (G91111), 1990-1994 (Box 141, Folder 27)
  - Harvard University - Branscomb-Kahin (G93113), 1992-1994 (Box 141, Folder 28)
  - Harvard University - Branscomb-Kahin (G93102), 1992-1994 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Harvard University - Program on Information Resources Policy - Oettinger (D94212), 1993-1996 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Harvard University - Center for Information Policy Research - Oettinger (D94208), 1993 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Harvard University - JFK School of Government - Branscomb-Kahin (G94115), 1993-1996 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - William Randolph Hearst Foundation, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Hebrew University, Jerusalem, 1976-1985 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - The Heritage Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 142, Folder 7-8)
  - Hertz Business Account Program, 1990 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1973-1996 (Box 142, Folder 10-14)
  - Manufacturers Hanover - Lee Morgan, 1990 (Box 142, Folder 15-22)
  - Markle Family - Mary Robinson Markle, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Markle Family - Dr. George B. Markle IV and Gordon Markle, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Markle Foundation on the Media and the Electorate, 1988-1994 (Box 142, Folder 25-27)
  - Markle Foundation - Sponsored Roundtable - Presidential Campaigns, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 28)
  - Markle Foundation - Website, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 29)
  - Market Opinion Research, 1989 (Box 142, Folder 30)
  - Market Opinion Research - John E. Polich, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 31)
  - Markle Foundation Programs, 1975-1989 (Box 142, Folder 32)
  - Gene Mater-John Adams Association (Radio and TV News Directors Association) (Box 142, Folder 33)
  - University of Maryland (Box 142, Folder 34-36)
  - MAXIS (Box 143, Folder 1-5)
  - MAXIS - SimHealth, 1993-1994 (Box 143, Folder 6-9)
  - McGraw Hill, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Media Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Media Research Center (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - MEGAVOICE - Larry Winters, 1989 (Box 143, Folder 13-14)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1976; 1990 (Box 143, Folder 15-16)
  - Mercantile Library, 1975; 1990 (Box 143, Folder 17-18)
  - Mercury Communications, England, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - University of Miami, 1974-1992 (Box 143, Folder 20-22)
  - University of Michigan, 1970-1980 (Box 143, Folder 23-25)
  - Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corporation, 1992-1995 (Box 143, Folder 26-27)
  - Microsoft Corporation, 1988-1994 (Box 143, Folder 28)
  - Mary Milton - Petersburg Inc. (Box 143, Folder 29)
  - Minnesota Public Radio Inc. - William Kling, 1976-1991 (Box 143, Folder 30)
  - Minnesota Public Programming Corp., 1977 (Box 143, Folder 31)
  - University of Minnesota, 1975-1994 (Box 143, Folder 32)
  - Minnesota Regional Cable Channel 6 - Peter Bradley, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 33)
  - Hector Miranda, 1987-1989 (Box 143, Folder 34)
    Restricted material - Personnel
  - Mitgang, Lee - General, 1997 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Mondale Policy Forum, 1991-1992 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Monitor Television, 1991 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Uwe Morawetz, 1991 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Morgan Stanley, 1991 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Motion Picture Association of America - Richard Heffner, 1979-1994 (Box 144, Folder 6-9)
  - Multimedia Corporation, 1991-1993 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Morgan, Janet, 1986-1988 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Museum of Television and Radio, 1991-1993 (Box 144, Folder 12-14)
  - Markle Foundation - TVV - Election Project (G90323) (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Markle Foundation - Trans-Atlantic Dialogue on European Broadcasting (D90319) (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Markle Foundation - Michael O'Neill (G90214) (Box 144, Folder 17-19)
  - Markle Foundation - Bruce Sidron (D90212) (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - Markle Foundation - Community Network-Brit. Telecom (D90211), 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - University of Maryland - Spicer (D90322) (Box 144, Folder 22)
  - University of Minnesota - Mondale Policy Forum (D92217) (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers (NYRAG) - Bryan (D92215), 1992 (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers (NYRAG) - Simmons (D91101) (Box 144, Folder 25)
  - North Carolina Agency for Public Communications, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 26)
  - Markle Foundation - SeniorNet - Furlong (G90324), 1990-1991 (Box 144, Folder 27)
  - Markle Foundation - SeniorNet - Furlong (G90324), 1991-1992 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - SeniorNet - Furlong (G92333) (Box 145, Folder 2-4)
  - N - General, 1989-1995 (Box 145, Folder 5-12)
  - National Council for Families and Television, 1989 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - National Electoral Sciences Institute (Willard), 1993 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - National Learning Center - Capital Children's Museum (Lewin), 1992 (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - National Opinion Research Center - Bradburn and Johnstone (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - National Public Telecomputing Network (Grundner), 1992 (Box 145, Folder 17-18)
  - The Nation Institute, 1990 (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - Mark Nadel - Common Carrier Video, 1989-1990 (Box 145, Folder 20-21)
  - National Academy Foundation, 1991 (Box 145, Folder 21A)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1996 (Box 145, Folder 22)
  - National Association of College Broadcasters, 1990 (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - National Association of Public Television Stations, 1985-1990 (Box 145, Folder 24)
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC), 1977-1991 (Box 145, Folder 25)
  - National Cable Television Association, Inc., 1976-1980 (Box 145, Folder 26)
  - National Issues Convention, 1991 (Box 145, Folder 27)
  - National Public Broadcasting Archives at the University of Maryland, 1991 (Box 145, Folder 28)
  - National Public Radio - General, 1978-1992 (Box 145, Folder 29-31)
  - National Urban Fellows, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - National Student-Parent Mock Election, 1988-1992 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Michael Newman (NewManWare), New Haven, CT, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - New York University (NYU), 1973-1992 (Box 146, Folder 4-7)
  - University of North Carolina, 1973-1993 (Box 146, Folder 8-12)
  - North Carolina Agency for Public Communications, 1992-1993 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Northwestern University, 1978-1996 (Box 146, Folder 14-16)
  - NSFRE - Los Angeles, 1994 September (Box 146, Folder 17)
  - O - General, 1975-1996 (Box 146, Folder 18-23)
  - OEF International, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 24)
  - Online Library Center, OCLC, 1989-1992 (Box 146, Folder 25)
  - Online Services (Box 146, Folder 26)
  - Oregon State University, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 27)
  - Karen Olson, 1988-1990 (Box 146, Folder 28)
  - University of Oxford, 1991 (Box 146, Folder 29)
  - Oxford University Press, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 30)
  - Ozark Mountain Softscapes, 1991 (Box 146, Folder 31)
  - P - General, 1994-1997 (Box 146, Folder 32-33)
  - P-Q - General, 1989-1990 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - P - General, 1991-1993 (Box 147, Folder 2-4)
  - Palo Alto Research Center, 1996 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1970-1978 (Box 147, Folder 6-10)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1990 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1991-1992 (Box 147, Folder 12-13)
  - Perkins, John A., 1987-1993 (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - Perlmutter, Alvin, 1991-1994 (Box 147, Folder 15-17)
  - Personnel Corporation of America, 1991-1993 (Box 147, Folder 18)
  - Pew Charitable Trust, 1990-1992 (Box 147, Folder 19-21)
  - Pew Research Center, 1996 (Box 147, Folder 22-24)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1983-1991 (Box 147, Folder 25-27)
  - Pocantico Conference Center, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 28)
  - Population Resource Center, 1990-1992 (Box 147, Folder 29)
  - Potomac Speakers Bureau, 1989 (Box 147, Folder 30)
  - Price Monroe (Moscow Law and Policy Center), 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 31)
  - Princeton University, 1971-1994 (Box 147, Folder 32-34)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates, 1992-1996 (Box 147, Folder 35-37)
  - Prodigy - Interactive Personnel Service, 1992-1995 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Promethee, 1988-1994 (Box 148, Folder 2-3)
  - Public Affairs Council, 1990 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Bill Moyers, 1989-1993 (Box 148, Folder 5-6)
  - Public Agenda Foundation - Wadsworth (D92216), 1992 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Public Agenda Foundation - Yankelovich, Wadsworth (D91113) (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Public Agenda Foundation, 1988-1996 (Box 148, Folder 9-17)
  - Public Broadcasting System, 1970-1990 (Box 148, Folder 18-24)
  - Public Broadcasting System, 1991-1996 (Box 149, Folder 1-7)
  - Public Policy Institute of California (David Lyons), 1994-1996 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - American Public Radio, 1989-1996 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - 2017:FA785:005 - American Public Radio Audio File, Vol. 1, No. 4, Audio cassette. (Box 2017:FA785:005)
  - Public Service Satellite Consortium, 1977-1991 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Public TV Initiative, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Purdue University, 1978-1992 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Purdue Research Foundation - Lenart (D91324), 1991-1995 (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Q - General, 1976-1995 (Box 149, Folder 14-16)
  - R - General, 1989-1997 (Box 149, Folder 17-25)
  - The Radio and Television News Directors Foundation (RTNDF), 1990-1996 (Box 149, Folder 26)
  - 2017:FA785:006 - The Radio and Television News Directors Foundation (RTNDF) - Follow the Money: Covering the 1996 Elections, Episode 96002, VHS, 30 minutes (Box 2017:FA785:006)
  - Radio for Youth Foundation - Pollack (D92102) (Box 149, Folder 27)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center - Grants, 1991-1992 (Box 149, Folder 28)
  - RAG Associates, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Random House, 1990 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1991 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Refugee Policy Group, 1986 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - REBUS, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Restivo Communications Group, 1992-1993 (Box 150, Folder 6-7)
  - The Responsive Community - Rights and Responsibilities (Etzioni) (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - The Charles Revson Foundation, 1979-1990 (Box 150, Folder 9-12)
  - Donald and Susan Rice, 1990-1991 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - University of Richmond, 1989-1992 (Box 150, Folder 14-15)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1986-1996 (Box 150, Folder 16-17)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1974-1996 (Box 150, Folder 18-22)
  - Rockefeller University, 1986-1990 (Box 150, Folder 23)
  - Rocky Mountain Media Watch (98-4074), 1997 (Box 150, Folder 24)
  - Joseph Roundtree Memorial Trust, 1990 (Box 150, Folder 25)
  - Run Fair, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 26)
  - Rutgers University (G92340), 1992-1994 (Box 150, Folder 27)
  - Rutgers University, 1974-1996 (Box 150, Folder 28-31)
  - Riverside Software Inc. (Grants Management Program), 1992 (Box 150, Folder 32)
  - Roper Organization, 1986-1991 (Box 150, Folder 33)
  - S - General, 1989-1997 (Box 150, Folder 34-42)
  - University of San Francisco, 1988-1989 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - San Diego State University, 1980-1990 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - University of San Francisco (97-3935), 1997 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - The Schechter Group, 1991 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Adam Kernan-Schloss, 1990-1992 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Gail Schwartz (Declassified Proposal), 1992 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Tony Schwartz (Declassified), 1992 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - 2017:FA785:007 - Guerrilla Media, VHS, 30 minutes (Box 2017:FA785:007)
  - Scientists' Institute for Public Administration, 1971-1993 (Box 151, Folder 8-10)
  - Startext - Participation with SeniorNet, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - SeniorNet, 1992-1997 (Box 151, Folder 12-15)
  - Shalala, Donna E. (Health and Human Services), 1993 (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - Shuman, Alfred J., 1997 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - Sierra Network, 1993 (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1969-1996 (Box 151, Folder 19-21)
  - Smithsonian, 1980-1992 (Box 151, Folder 22)
  - Social Science Research on Cable, 1973-1994 (Box 151, Folder 23)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1971-1989 (Box 151, Folder 24)
  - Society for Applied Learning Technology, 1990 (Box 151, Folder 24A)
  - Solomons, Seth, 1996 (Box 151, Folder 25)
  - South Bank Business School, 1993 (Box 151, Folder 26)
  - University of Southern California, 1972-1994 (Box 151, Folder 27-32)
  - University of South Carolina, 1994 (Box 151, Folder 33)
  - Southern Methodist University, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 34)
  - Southern Regional Conference, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 35)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1976-1995 (Box 151, Folder 36-37)
  - Southport Institute for Policy Analysis (SIPA), 1990-1994 (Box 151, Folder 38-39)
  - Spencer Stuart (Executive Search Consultants), 1987-1993 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Spencer Foundation, 1973-1983 (Box 152, Folder 2-5)
  - Stanford University - Noll (G90215), 1990-1994 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University, 1970-1995 (Box 152, Folder 7-15)
  - Stanford University - Center for Economic Policy Research, 1990-1994 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Stanford University - Center for Study of Language and Information, 1988-1990 (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Stanford University - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Frank Staton, 1984 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Fred Starr, 1991 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Statistical Research, Inc., 1991-1997 (Box 152, Folder 21-27)
  - Stratosphere (Box 152, Folder 28)
  - Stein Gerontological Center, 1987-1991 (Box 153, Folder 1-2)
  - Stevens Institute of Technology, 1987-1991 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Sundra Foundation, 1992-1995 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Syracuse University, 1982-1994 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Syracuse University - Patterson (G92108), 1991-1993 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - T - General (Box 153, Folder 7-10)
  - Taconic Foundation, 1997 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - The Taft Group, 1990 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Tarrant County, Fort Worth Texas, 1988-1989 (Box 153, Folder 13-15)
  - TCI, 1995 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - TCN, 1991-1992 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Telecommunications Policy Research Conference (TPRC) - Panzar (G92343), 1980-1995 (Box 153, Folder 18-19)
  - Telecommunications Cooperative Network, Inc., 1980-1989 (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - Telematics, 1994 (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - Telesearch, 1988 (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - TERC-Tinker, 1987-1992 (Box 153, Folder 23-26)
  - Texas Southern University, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 27)
  - University of Texas, Austin, 1970-1996 (Box 153, Folder 28-30)
  - University of Texas, Austin - Williams (D92330), 1992-1993 (Box 153, Folder 31)
  - University of Texas - Sherman (G92111) (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - University of Texas, Austin - Williams (D91106), 1990-1992 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - University of Texas, Austin - Williams, 1986-1990 (Box 154, Folder 3-4)
  - University of Texas, Dallas - Harpole, 1980-1982 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - University of Texas, Austin, 1993-1994 (Box 154, Folder 6-7)
  - Thinking Tools - Election '96 Project, 1994-1996 (Box 154, Folder 8-13)
  - The Times Mirror Center, 1994-1995 (Box 154, Folder 14-15)
  - Times Mirror Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Time-Warner, 1991-1996 (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - Peter Tops, 1991-1992 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - The Travelers, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - T - General, 1970-1984 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - Tufts University, 1990 (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - Turner Broadcasting System, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - Turner Educational Services, Inc., 1992 (Box 154, Folder 23)
  - Twenthieth Century Fund, 1970-1994 (Box 155, Folder 1-11)
  - U-V - General, 1990-1994 (Box 155, Folder 12-15)
  - U.S. Conference of Mayors - Cochran (93-59), 1992 (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce - National Institute of Standards and Technology, 1989 (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Department of Justice (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, 1990 (Box 155, Folder 19)
  - The Union Institute, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 20)
  - Universal Email, 1994 (Box 155, Folder 21)
  - V - General, 1989-1996 (Box 155, Folder 22-25)
  - Vanderbilt University, 1970-1990 (Box 155, Folder 26-27, 27A)
  - Vemeer, Inc., 1995 (Box 155, Folder 28)
  - Video Technologies International (91-45), 1990 (Box 155, Folder 29)
  - University of Virginia, 1978-1996 (Box 155, Folder 30-32)
  - Voice of America (Geoffry Cowan), 1994 (Box 155, Folder 33)
  - The Voters Channel, 1989-1992 (Box 155, Folder 34-35)
  - The Voyager Company, 1993-1996 (Box 155, Folder 36-37)
  - W - General, 1989-1997 (Box 155, Folder 38-44)
  - Wake Forest University, 1990 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Walt Disney Company, 1989-1990 (Box 156, Folder 2-3)
  - Ward Howell International (Runqvist), 1993-1995 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Wall Street Journal, 1995 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - University of Washington, Seattle, 1973-1990 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Washington University, St. Louis, 1975-1988 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Waynesburg College - Beasley, 1976 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - WBAI - Goodman and Kosof, 1975-1977 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Daniel Webster, 1989 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Washington Center for Policy Research (Henry Geller), 1993-1994 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Washington Post, 1991-1992 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - Washington State, Pullman, WA, 1984 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - Washington State, 1977-1982 (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - Washington Journalism Center, 1971 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - Western Behavioral Science Institute (WBSI), 1984-1991 (Box 156, Folder 16-17)
  - WETA, 1980-1994 (Box 156, Folder 18-20)
  - WGBH, 1977-1994 (Box 156, Folder 21-22)
  - WHYY, Philadelphia, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 23)
  - The Woodrow Wilson Center, 1982-1991 (Box 156, Folder 24-25)
  - Congressman Timothy E. Wirth, 1983-1984 (Box 156, Folder 26)
  - Senator Timothy E. Wirth, 1989-1992 (Box 156, Folder 27)
  - WNET - Thirteen, 1977-1993 (Box 156, Folder 28-30)
  - WNCN, 1987 (Box 156, Folder 31)
  - WNYC, 1989-1990 (Box 156, Folder 32)